if you're looking for a home in the
temple belt in area with a pool solar
panels and three car garage I've got the
home for you welcome to living in
Central Texas I'm Andrea dudic realtor
and Associate broker with Vista Real
Estate and I cannot wait to show you
this home let's take a look
down
[Music]
thank you so much for joining me on this
wonderful home tour today homes in this
price point with all of these features
are really hard to find so if you'd like
to take a look or see any more just like
this you can find all my contact
information below let's book a call and
check out some homes if you love this
home go ahead and head on over to my
other video at 838 mosqu Drive In belon
that one is a luxury listing with a pool
and pickle ball cart till next time
[Music]